

Georgi Dimitrov

Software Developer

About Me

Dedicated and proficient Software Developer with more than 5 years of experience in programming. Recent Computer Science graduate looking for his next endeavor. Eager to apply his skill and create or improve software products. Capable of working independently or in team to solve problems. Analyzing and innovating existing products.

Professional Experience

Musala Soft | Internship

June 2019 - July 2019

Key points:

- Developed a virtual wallet app in a team of two for budgeting.
- Got training on how the company employees work from the company trainer.
- Got an endorsement letter from the lead trainer based on my performance.

Make Impact | Internship

July 2022 - January 2023

Key points:

- · Changed completely the design of the company mobile app.
- Restructured the code architecture to follow best practices.
- Refactored a huge amount of code to follow the same code style and structure.
- Removed all the redundant code and cleared up the app boosting its performance.
- Coded an identical copy of the app in React Native since the original app was written in React.

Education

KEA - Copenhagen School of Design and Technology

AP Computer Science Degree

August 2020 - January 2023

Key points:

- Studied different aspects of software development such as Software Design, Business values, Project Management, etc.
- Developed numerous projects using different technologies throughout the semesters.
- Learned to learn how to do things independently.
- Had elective courses in React Native, Node JS, Machine Learning.

National program by the Bulgarian Ministry of Education

IT career education

October 2017 - June 2020

Key points:

- Part of the courses I had were OOP, Algorithms, Data Structures, Functional programming, etc.
- Studied primarily C# with its ASP.NET Core framework but also Haskell, and C++ in some of the courses.
- Graduated with 5.26 out of 6 and got EQF Level 3 Certificate for "Applied programming".





georgi.dimitrov.1112@gmail.com

() +45 50 20 95 27

in linkedin.com/in/georgi-dim

github.com/solvemate2018

Programming Skills



Frameworks



SQL SQL Server

PostgreSQL MongoDB

Firebase AWS (VM hosting)

Docker Git Google Cloud



Georgi Dimitrov Software Developer

Volunteering

AIESEC in Copenhagen

Account Manager

October 2021 - January 2022

Key points:

- I was making sure that the partners I was managing were as happy as possible with our service.
- Worked in a team of four with a leader that was teaching us every week new aspects of the job.
- Together with account managing, I was doing also sales for the organisation, trying to find new partners.

AIESEC in Copenhagen

Regional Manager of Operations

January 2022 - January 2023

Key points:

- Led a team of 4 people whose purpose was to ensure the customer satisfaction of all the people we were working with.
- Had been audited every month if all the customer standards we had were covered and got 0 Violations for the whole year.
- Trained all of the new recruits for my team about what the organization was all about and how to do their job properly.

Soft Skills

Communication

Critical thinking

Problem-solving

Willingness to learn

Positive attitude

Reliability

Teamwork

Dedication

Logical thinking

Languages

English
Full Professional Proficiency

Bulgarian
Native Proficiency

German Elementary Proficiency

AIESEC in Copenhagen

Regional Manager of Business Development

August 2022 - January 2023

Key points:

- Took over the position after the previous manager left the organization unexpectedly.
- Revived the department by leaving it with 4 trained business development people, one of whom replaced me as a manager.
- Couldn't achieve my goals for the duration but I left a structured team after starting from scratch.

@ Certificates

Cambridge English: Advanced January 2020

AP Computer Science Degree *January 2023*

EQF Level 3 Certificate for "Applied programming" *June 2020*